gaiagps.com 2019-12-04

# Gaia GPS - Privacy Policy

**Collection of Information.**

Personal Information

By their nature, the Services track certain data from your mobile device that may be used to identify you individually. Such data may include, but is not limited to, routes, tracks, waypoints and geo-tagged photos that you take while out hiking, mountain biking, and offroading. When registering to use the Services, we may also require you to provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your name, company/organization name, email address, and/or social media username (these are referred to below as your "Personal Contact Information").

When purchasing the Services, we will require you to provide financial and billing information, such as billing name and address, and credit card number ("Billing Information"). Your Personal Contact Information and your Billing Information, together with any other information we gather through the Services that may be used to identify, contact, or locate you individually, are collectively referred to herein as your "Personal Information."

Data, Diagnostic & Login Information

You may be able to create, upload, publish, transmit, distribute, display, store or share information, data, text, graphics, photos, video, messages, maps or other materials using our Services (this is collectively referred to below as "Data"). Some of this Data may be stored and maintained on our servers. Through the Services, you will have the ability to select that some or all of your Data be made available to other users. Data that you select to be made available to other users shall be referred to as "Public Data." Any Data that you do not affirmatively indicate through the Services to be designated Public Data will be deemed "Private Data." If you run into technical errors in the course of using the Services, we will automatically obtain a crash report along with certain logging information from your system documenting the error ("Diagnostic Information"). You may opt out of providing such Diagnostic Information, in your discretion.  Such information may contain information regarding your Operating System version, hardware, browser version (and .NET version information in case of Windows systems), and your email address, if provided.  Additionally, certain login information may be maintained in a cookie stored locally on your personal computing device (i.e. not on a server) in order to streamline the login process ("Login Information").

Usage and Analytics Information

As you use our Services, we may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies, log files, and Web beacons. Such Information may include standard information regarding your mobile device, browser type, browser language, Operating System, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and the actions you take on our web site (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked) or while using the Services. Collectively, this information is referred to as "Usage and Analytics Information."

Geo-Location Information

When you use our Services, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location. Such information is referred to as "Geo-Location Information." If you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth below, you can turn off the location tracking option for the Services located in your account settings, or otherwise in your mobile phone settings.

**Disclosures & Transfers.**  We have put in place contractual and other organizational safeguards with our agents to ensure a proper level of protection of your Personal Information (see further "Security" below).  In addition to those measures, we will not disclose or transfer your Personal Information to third parties without your permission, except as specified in this Privacy Policy (see further below). 

Please note that if you are using the Services at the request or as part of an organization, your organization’s account administrator may be able to view certain activity and content associated with use of the Services, including, but not limited to, elements of your Personally Identifiable Information.

From time to time we may employ third parties to help us provide and/or improve the Services.  These third parties may have limited access to databases of user information or registered member information solely for the purpose of helping us to provide and/or improve the Services and they will be subject to contractual restrictions prohibiting them from using the information about our users for any other purpose.  Except as specifically set forth below, such agents or third parties do not have any rights to use Personal Information beyond what is absolutely necessary to assist us.

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your consent if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of the Services, or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities.  We may disclose Personal Information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law.

We may also disclose your Personal Information in connection with a corporate re-organization, a merger or amalgamation with another entity, a sale of all or a substantial portion of our assets or stock, including any due diligence exercise carried out in relation to the same, provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.
